webforpc.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy - Latest Version Download

**Privacy Policy for** **[www.webforpc.com](https://webforpc.com/).**

The EU’s new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) comes into effect on May 25th, 2018. This is an exciting new epoch for your data privacy. We wanted to let you comprehend that we have taken measures to assure, that we maintain a safe and compliant system for our visitors, an example of which is the **new data retention system**. Data security is always our top priority. You can get more information by reading our privacy policy contained within this page.

This page includes all the processes through which **WebForPC** collects user information and the way it’s being utilized. At **WebForPC.COM  **user’s privacy is our prime concern, hence policy contained herein would apply to all the products and services offered by the www.webforpc.com. As this website uses Google products that incorporate this policy, so we have to ensure that certain disclosures are given to, and consents obtained from, end users in the European Economic Area.

#### **What Are Cookies:**

The Cookies – small text files that are placed on your Computer to help the site delivering better user experience. In general, cookies are used to preserve user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymized tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. in general, cookies are there to make your browsing experience better. However, you are allowed to disable cookies on this site and others. The most comfortable way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We advise consulting the Help section of the browser or taking a look at [  **About Cookies website**](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)  which provides guidance for all modern browsers.

#### **Switching Off The Cookies**

#### **Collection of The Personal Information & Opting-Out**

We never force users to disclose their personal information, But such information such as Browser info, and Location (through Log Files) is required by the website to track its performance and to implement and utilize better ways to enhance users experience and website’s quality. An example medium through which we monitor such information is “Google Analytics” which is extremely helpful for us to track site’s activity on the daily, weekly or monthly basis. GA helps us to collect the certain statistics which are required to ensure content quality and to improve the website’s quality accordingly. But your personal identification is assured to be safeguarded at WebForPC as far as its being disclosed to us only. Our visitors may opt out of Google Analytics by using the opt-out service provided by Google:  **[Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)**.

For data collection through “Google Analytics,” we have set the new limit to for the analytics to retain the data and its deletion. When data touches the end of the retention limit, it is deleted automatically on a monthly basis. We have set the **data retention limit to “14 Months”** which is basically the period after which the data will be automatically deleted from the analytics account.

#### **Cookies & Advertisements**

We only display ads (solely) from **Google Adsense**  (no ads from any third party advertising networks) which utilizes cookies (Double-Click) to deliver its services, while being a third party service provider, Ads served by Google Adsense are no way in our control, so we are not responsible for that. But being a mighty network, we trust the services provided by Google; still one may go with opting out of the cookies by visiting detailed privacy policy laid down by a competent authority at  **<https://policies.google.com/>**.Again! We use Google AdSense, and they serve ads on our site based on a user’s prior visits to our website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its official partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. **Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie** for interest-based advertising by visiting  **[Ads Settings](https://webforpc.com/cookie-policy/)**. Alternatively, users can opt-out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting  **[aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)**.If WebForPC.com use other advertising networks (other than Google AdSense), their privacy policies will always be listed on their official (respective) sites. Most of these companies belong to the Network Advertising Initiative. Our visitors may opt-out of behavioral advertising methods by visiting [ **networkadvertising.org**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

#### **Linkage to Third Party Sites**

Sometimes we provide links leading to official websites (Out Bound Links) for the convenience and knowledge of our users, but we are in no way affiliated to them in any way, and these third-party sites are no way related to us, and we do not take any responsibility for the record of personal information and the way it is going to be used, by such sites.

#### **Mailing List**

WebForPC never dispatches any unsolicited Emails/Promotional Plans/Advertising etc., through our mailing system. We only deliver the freshly published content through our website (Software Reviews & Trial Downloads), and users are in complete control to “Subscribe” or to “Unsubscribe” our mailing list.

#### **Bound to Secure the Users Data**

We are officially and legally obliged to ensure that the usage of the data or stats collected through this website solely for the purposes mentioned above. The metrics to gather the data are systematic and we have taken all measures to make sure that the figures or any information collected are to be used only for the above-mentioned legitimate purposes.

This privacy policy is specially intended to inform  **EU Users** and also other viewers from the whole world, that by visiting or using our services you are giving the implied consent to the data collection terms if no steps to opt-out (as guided above) will be taken on the part of users. For easy access, we have made this privacy statement a part of our **Top Menu Bar.**

We are the ones, who are bound to amend this privacy policy at any time, especially in the case where we will be collecting the user’s data in any other mean (in addition to the mentioned ones).

#### **Revision of this Privacy Policy**

Infrequently, we may change this privacy policy (or other records related to privacy policy) to enable WebForPC to use or share your data differently. If we do, the links to the policy on our websites (which are generally found in the footer of the site) will indicate that the policy has been changed. For users, the change will become effective upon accepting our policy prompt bar displaying at every page. We urge you to rhythmically examine the privacy policy for the newest information on our privacy disciplines.

If you have concerns, suggestions, and queries relating Privacy Policy of WebForPC.Com, feel free to send us an email at webforpc@gmail.com.

_**This Statement is Last Updated on 24th of May 2018.**_
